torycomics.com 2019-07-21

# ToryComics_Privacy

[ToryComics] Privacy Policy

Created: April 25, 2017

ToryWorks, Corp. (“TORYCOMICS”) respects the privacy rights of its users and protects the personal information collected, stored and used in connection with our service (our "Service"). To further this commitment, we have adopted this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to guide how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us.  
By accessing our Service, including registering for a TORYCOMICS account, downloading and using software made available by TORYCOMICS, or by clicking the “I accept” button (or its equivalent), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not register for an account with TORYCOMICS, download software made available by TORYCOMICS, or otherwise access our Service.

1\. SCOPE OF PRIVACY POLICY  
This Privacy Policy describes TORYCOMICS’s collection and use of personal information submitted and collected through our Service. Personal information includes any individually identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address, and information concerning you collected and/or maintained in personally identifiable form.  
Please be aware that advertisers or websites with links to and from our Service may collect personal information about you. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, those other advertisers or websites.

2\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
We may collect and process the following data about you:  
• Personal information such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card number when you register for an account with TORYCOMICS, make sales inquiries, request support, or make a purchase or payment.  
• We collect certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, operating system, browser type, date/time stamp, and/or program or system error messages and other system information. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you to improve our Service, to improve marketing, analytics, or website functionality.  
• If you contact us or respond to messages and communications that we send to you, we may keep a record of that correspondence.  
• We collect details of your use of our Service and the resources that you access. Such usage information includes information about how, when and from where you access or use our Service.  
• User feedback, community discussions, chats and other interactions on our Service.  
• If you access our Service on your mobile telephone or other mobile device, including tablets, we collect mobile device identifiers, including MAC Address, and IP Address. Certain aspects of our Service will create and assign to your device an identifier that is similar to an account number. We may collect the name you have associated with your device, device type, telephone number, country, and any other information you choose to provide or allow us to access, such as geo-location.

3\. TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES & COOKIES  
TORYCOMICS and our partners, such as marketing partners and analytics providers, may use tracking technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering our websites, tracking users’ movements around the websites, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We use cookies for various purposes including our shopping cart, to remember users’ settings, and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies by adjusting individual browser settings. However, if you reject cookies, you may still use our websites, but your ability to use some features or areas of our websites may be limited.  
We may also use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. For this reason, these types of clear gifs are tied to personally identifiable information.  
We may also use tools or third party analytical software to automatically collect and use certain non-personal information that does not directly enable TORYCOMICS to identify you.

4\. USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION COLLECTED  
We use your personal information and non-personal information, both individually or combined together:  
• To help us manage, operate and deliver our Service to you  
• To improve your experience with our Service  
• To develop new products or services for you  
• To provide you with customer and technical support  
• To provide you with software updates  
• To communicate with you about our Service (unless you have not consented to allow us to use your information for these purposes)  
• For marketing and promotional purposes  
• For internal training purposes and statistical analysis  
TORYCOMICS does not sell or rent your personal information to third-parties for marketing purposes without your consent. However, you hereby agree that TORYCOMICS may share your personal information with our affiliates to provide you our Service or information about other services and promotional materials. In addition, TORYCOMICS may share personal information with third party service providers that assist TORYCOMICS in providing you our Service. As a result, your information may be transferred to countries outside your residence.  
When we share your personal information with third party vendors and suppliers, we require them to adhere to confidentiality and non-disclosure obligations.  
If the ownership or control of all or part of our Service or their assets changes, we may transfer your personal information to the new owner.  
Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personal information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose personal information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation.

5\. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES OR SERVICES  
You should be aware that our Service may from time to time contain links to third-party sites, products or services. TORYCOMICS is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites or services. If you are concerned about the privacy policy of a certain third party, you should read the privacy policy of the site or service to which you link before you submit any personal information.  
We may also use Google remarketing services, which allow third parties, including Google, to serve advertisements to you on our behalf based on your activity on our Service. This involves placing in certain areas of our Service a small piece of code provided by Google. This code enables third parties, including Google, to place a cookie on your computer that tells them about your use of our Service and allows them to recognize you and display relevant advertisements when you visit other websites within the Google Display Network. We may also use similar remarketing services from other companies. If you would like to opt-out of Google Analytics collecting data from your browser when you visit websites, you can download and install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on here:https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/

6\. ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION  
TORYCOMICS makes good faith efforts to enable you to review, update or correct your personal information in our possession. In order to do so, please log into your account or contact our Privacy Policy Administrator at [help@toryworks.com](mailto:help@toryworks.com). If you contact us, we will need sufficient information from you to establish your identity and to verify your access request, and also to assist us in handling your request. Please note that even if personal information is changed or deleted according to your request, TORYCOMICS may still retain some of your personal information to resolve disputes, enforce TORYCOMICS user agreement(s), and comply with technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our Service.

7\. DEACTIVATED OR TERMINATED ACCOUNTS  
A request to delete and/or terminate your account will not result in the removal of information collected and already put in aggregate form or information that cannot, in our sole discretion, be removed without undue burden to us. We are not able nor are we obligated to remove any of your information from a third party provider or platform. Moreover, please be aware that even after you delete your account or your account is terminated, your information may not be deleted in its entirety from our servers and servers of the third party with whom such information have been shared

8\. INQUIRIES  
If you have any questions, please feel free to e-mail us at [help@toryworks.com](mailto:help@toryworks.com).
